http://www.mountainbaby.com/pages/privacy-policy

Shipping is now only $10 in Canada! Excludes Heavy Items & "Remote" Areas. Click here for COVID 19 information.Advent sale on now! Day 10: 10% off Hape Railway Sets!*Discount taken at checkout*
(PST) Monday to Saturday10am-5pmClosed Sundays & Holidays636 Baker St,
Nelson BC
CAD
USD
AUD
1 (888) 990-2292
info@mountainbaby.com
My Account
Welcome to Mountain Baby!
Login
Create Account
0
Home
Sale Items
Catalog
Baby & Toddler Basics
Baby & Toddler Toys
Music & Instruments
Made In BC!
Shop By Brand
A
4M Education
Ambler
Ania
Aqua Lung
Around The Crib
Avanchy
Shopping Cart
Your cart is currently empty.
Continue Shopping
My Account
Welcome to Mountain Baby!
Login
Create Account
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
MOUNTAIN BABY'S PRIVACY POLICY
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. You can always just visit our site anonymously.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, mailing address, phone number and email address. When ordering by phone you will be asked for your credit card number.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: • To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)• To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)• To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)• To process transactions.• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature• To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. In addition, at your request, it can be used for receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards etc.) will not be stored on our servers.Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We, therefore, will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at any time by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on May 21, 2018.Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. www.mountainbaby.com
Mountain Baby
636 Baker StreetNelson, British Columbia V1L 4J4Canadainfo@mountainbaby.com250 352 17891 888 990 2292
Click & Pick Up
Please note, Click & Pick Up is only available at our 2 retail outlets, located in Nelson and Rossland, in British Columbia, Canada.
Keep in Touch
Sign up for our newsletter and be the first to know about coupons and special promotions.
About us
Mountain Baby was born (and still lives) in the fabulous mountain town of Nelson, British Columbia, Canada. For over 20 years, we've been providing families with the things they need to be in nature, be active, and thrive together.
Visit the store!
636 Baker St.
Nelson BC, Canada
Click here to read our story.
Customer Service
Click here for COVID information.If you have questions, comments, concerns, or just want to say hi, please drop us a line!
Call us: (250) 352-1789 or toll free in North America 1 (888) 990-2292
Click here to get in touch with us.
Our Shipping Policy.
Our Return Policy.
Our Privacy Policy.
Store Hours (PST) Monday to Saturday: 10am - 5pm Closed Sundays & Holidays
© 2020 Mountain Baby
